Project Context
You are building an autonomous AI agent for a course project.
Domain: Language Schools
Problem:
Language learners lack authentic practice in modern slang and informal conversation. Teachers and textbooks are formal and outdated, while learners want to speak like people on TikTok, gaming platforms, and real life.
Solution Overview:
An AI agent that simulates realistic, slang-based conversations, adapts to the user’s proficiency, and generates scenario-based dialogue practice using real-world conversational data (Reddit via RAG).
The system is agent-based, supervised, and optimized to minimize LLM calls.
The different agents have to utilize reasoning abilities and make autonomous decisions based on give information.
High-Level Architecture (Must Match Diagram Exactly)
The architecture contains the following modules (names are strict and must not change):
1. SupervisorAgent
o Orchestrates the flow
o Decides which sub-agent to invoke
o Aggregates final response
o Leading the conversation with the user
2. ProgramPlanner (Plan & Execute Agent)
o Breaks the user request into steps
o Decides learning objective and conversation structure
3. SystemCritic (Reflection Agent)
o Reviews generated dialogue
o Ensures slang authenticity, safety, clarity, and level appropriateness
o Decide when to finish the conversation
4. ScenarioArchitect
o Builds realistic conversation scenarios based on the retrived data and the user profile
o Pre decided scenarios for fast conversation start
o Uses RAG over Reddit dataset for informal language patterns
5. UserEvaluation (ReAct Agent)
o Interacts with the user during conversation
o Adapts difficulty based on performance
o Updates proficiency level
o Produce a summery after each conversation with main users mistakes and future tips and workplan. Also, compare to previous talks and mention weather the user is improving his language level or not.
Databases (Required)
• Supabase
o User Information DB – need to generate realistic user profiles (10 profiles)
o Proficiency Level DB
• Pinecone
o Vector DB for Reddit embeddings (RAG)

Core Technical Requirements (DO NOT VIOLATE)
Optimization Rules
• Avoid unnecessary LLM calls
• Cache:
o Retrieved Reddit chunks
o User proficiency
• Keep prompts minimal and structured
• Stay within $13 total LLMod.ai budget

Required API Endpoints (MUST MATCH EXACTLY)

GET /api/team_info
Returns static team information.
{
  "group_batch_order_number": "X_Y",
  "team_name": "Your Team Name",
  "students": [
    { "name": "Student A", "email": "a@..." },
    { "name": "Student B", "email": "b@..." },
    { "name": "Student C", "email": "c@..." }
  ]
}

GET /api/agent_info
Explain what the agent does and how to use it.
Must include:
• Description
• Purpose
• Prompt template
• Prompt examples with full responses
• Steps list matching architecture modules
{
  "description": "...",
  "purpose": "...",
  "prompt_template": {
    "template": "..."
  },
  "prompt_examples": [
    {
      "prompt": "Example prompt",
      "full_response": "Agent output",
      "steps": ["SupervisorAgent", "ProgramPlanner", "..."]
    }
  ]
}

GET /api/model_architecture
Returns PNG image of the architecture diagram.
• Content-Type: image/png
• Must visually match:
o Supervisor
o Sub-agents
o Databases
• Module names must be identical to code & logs

POST /api/execute (MAIN ENTRY POINT)
{
  "prompt": "User request"
}
Success Response
{
  "status": "ok",
  "error": null,
  "response": "Final agent response",
  "steps": [
    {
      "module": "ProgramPlanner",
      "prompt": {},
      "response": {}
    }
  ]
}

Error Response
{
  "status": "error",
  "error": "Human-readable message",
  "response": null,
  "steps": []
}






Steps Logging Rules
For every LLM call, log:
• module
• exact prompt
• exact response
No hidden calls allowed.
Frontend (Required, Minimal)
Build a simple web UI:
Required:
• Once the user opens the system, he needs to choose his user profile from a list of pre-generated user profiles.
• Based on the user profile he is given a list of scenarios to choose from or write in his own words the scenario and based on that scenario the conversation will follow.
• “Run Agent” button
• Text area for user responses during chat
• Display:
o Final response
o Full steps trace (module + prompt + response)
• Conversation history
• Conversation summery and evaluation
• Chat-like display
Keep UI simple and debugging-oriented.

Recommended Project Structure
/backend
  /agents
    supervisor.py
    planner.py
    critic.py
    scenario_architect.py
    user_evaluation.py
  /api
    routes.py
  /rag
    reddit_retriever.py
  /db
    supabase.py
    pinecone.py
  main.py
/frontend
  index.html
  app.js
  styles.css
/assets
  architecture.png
Deployment Rules
• Deploy on Render
• Backend must be public
• Keep deployment alive until graded
• Store secrets in environment variables
Cursor Behavior Rules
When implementing:
1. Start with backend skeleton
2. Implement endpoints first (mock logic)
3. Then implement agents incrementally
4. Always keep architecture & step logging consistent
5. Never rename modules without updating:
o Architecture diagram
o /api/model_architecture
o /api/execute steps
Goal Reminder
This is not a chatbot.
This is a reasoning-based, modular AI agent that:
• Plans
• Retrieves real informal language
• Generates realistic dialogue
• Reflects and adapts
• Explains its reasoning

